[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which famous hoax of the early twentieth century fooled many including Sir Arthur Conan Doyle?", "correct_answer": "The Cottingley Fairies.", "incorrect_answers": ["Will-o-the-Wisp", "The Amherst haunting.", "The Cock Lane ghost."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many unsuccessful attempts did it take to finally create Dolly, the first successfully cloned mammal?", "correct_answer": "276", "incorrect_answers": ["76", "19", "154"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of cake is also known as the King of Cakes?", "correct_answer": "Baumkuchen", "incorrect_answers": ["Genoise Cake", "Queen Elisabeth cake", "Croquembouche"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the British Prime Minister on February 14th 1940?", "correct_answer": "Chamberlain", "incorrect_answers": ["Callaghan", "Churchill", "Canning"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie directed by Stanley Kubrick was nominated for seven Academy Awards?", "correct_answer": "Barry Lyndon", "incorrect_answers": ["Fear and Desire", "2001: A Space Odyssey", "Spartacus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Shenandoah Valley in western Virginia derives its name from a Native American expression meaning what?", "correct_answer": "Beautiful Daughter of the Stars", "incorrect_answers": ["Beautiful Daughter of the Fields", "Beautiful Mother of the Fruits", "Beautiful Mother of the Land"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What part of the grape plant contains the lowest amount of antioxidants?", "correct_answer": "Leaves", "incorrect_answers": ["Pulp of the fruit", "Skin of the fruit", "Seeds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The largest city in what US state hosts Summerfest, or The Worlds Largest Music Festival?", "correct_answer": "Wisconsin", "incorrect_answers": ["New Jersey", "Kentucky", "Maryland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "An artist painted a 60 ft. tall image of a naked woman above a tunnel in Malibu Canyon in 1966.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Massachusetts born musical composer wrote Sleigh Ride, Holiday for Strings, The Typewriter and Plink, Plank, Plunk.", "correct_answer": "Leroy Anderson", "incorrect_answers": ["John Cage", "John Fiedler", "Walter Piston"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The actors playing Diana Christiansen and Howard Beale in this Sidney Lumet movie won Academy Awards.", "correct_answer": "Network", "incorrect_answers": ["Ordinary People", "American Beauty", "Out of Africa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The coyote lives in North America and also goes by this name.", "correct_answer": "Prairie Wolf", "incorrect_answers": ["Desert Dog", "Prairie Dog", "Small Wolf"]}]